## Fernado Zamorano

Mexicali, México · Fernando Zamorano | LinkedIn · +52 688 10 72 811 · SoyFerxd@proton.me

Over 5 years of experience as a Front-End Developer. My goal is to continue learning and improving my skills as a developer, with a focus on creating efficient and optimized code.

## **Professional Experience**

PureCode AI Remote

FrontEnd UI Designer

June 2022–December 2022

- Designed pages and sub-pages using Tailwind CSS and MUI.
- Created, maintained, and optimized JSX components exclusively with React.

Pretendo Network Remote

Web Developer March 2023–Dec. 2023

- Designed main pages and sub-pages using pure CSS.
- Provided support in JavaScript development using the Express framework (NodeJS).

S-FX Remote

Web Developer Dec. 2023–February 2024

- Designed pages and sub-pages using Bootstrap and Font Awesome.
- Created, maintained, and optimized JSX components with React, ViteJS, and AstroJS.

## **EDUCATION**

UTEL Universidad Remote

Computer Engineering 2021 - Present

## Additional skills

• Native in Spanish and fluent English